kickass.com 2005-04-06

# Privacy @ Kick Ass

## Our Commitment To Privacy 

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

## The Information We Collect & How We Use It 

When submitting an order directly through KickAssPictures.com we may collect your name, address, contact information, and when needed, billing information. When your personal information is collected at KickAssPictures.com it will be used soley by Kick Ass Pictures, Inc. for the purpose of filling your order, contacting you with regards to your order, following up on your order if necessary, and unless you specify otherwise, marketing our products to you in the future. **We do not share personal information with ANY third parties.**

When applying for a membership to "members-only" areas of KickAssPictures.com, your personal information is collected by CCBILL LTD . Please see their Privacy Policy concerning collected information. For customer support purposes, [CCBILL LTD](http://www.ccbill.com/) may make some of your personal information (this is limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail, and payment method only) available to us. **We do not share your personal information with ANY third parties.**

When renting DivX rental movies on KickAssPictures.com at http://www.kickasspictures.com/divx/ , your personal information is collected by [IBILL](http://www.ibill.com/) . Please see their Privacy Policy concerning collected information. For customer support purposes, IBILL may make some of your personal information (this is limited to your name, address, phone number, e-mail, and payment method only) available to us. **We do not share your personal information with ANY third parties.**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Kick Ass Pictures, Inc.'s KickAssPictures.com website. 

## Our Commitment To Data Security 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

## How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information 

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us using the methods described below. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

## How To Contact Us 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 323-981-1700 or send us an email at [support@kickasspictures.com](mailto:support@kickasspictures.com) .
